

100 East 357 Street Auckland, New-Zealand 514 557-1532

kevinbla combe@outlook.com

https://kevin00785.github.io/portfolio/

BIOGRAPHY

I'm 34 years old web developer and product creator from the cozy streets of Montreal. I have two strong years of work experience in web agency and freelance projects. I love traveling, playing guitar, spend time with friends as much as my career. For me, developing websites is not a job but a passion.



EXPERIENCE

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER

Anekdotes Comm. | Nov 2017 - Jul 2019

As a front end developer & integrator, my main tasks were the integration of mock-ups. SEO, maintenance and much more..

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER - INTERNSHIP

Anekdotes Comm. | Sep 2017 - Nov 2017

My first internship in a web & marketing agency. They hired me due to my continuous learning process and personality.

TRAVEL AND WORK ABROAD

Several Positions | Oct 2012 - Oct 2015

Around the world, I worked several positions especially in hospitality, barista and english teacher

EDUCATION

WEB DEVELOPMENT - ONLINE COURSES

Udemy | Sep 2017 - Now

Being an autodidact, I took online courses during my spare time. Like React, VueJS, Bem, Vanilla JavaScript, etc.

WEB DEVELOPMENT & DESIGN DEGREE

Maisonneuve College | Oct 2015 - Nov 2017

Renowned technology school in Montreal, I learned the concepts of programming and designing web application.

TEACHING ENGLISH AS A FOREIGN LANGUAGE

Ittt, International TEFL and TESOL training

During a trip in Vietnam, I took online courses to become an english teacher.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Born in Montreal, Canada. Learned english and spanish in college and while travelling abroad.





SPANISH 30%



SKILLS

Html5-Css3-Sass-Bem

JavaScript-Jquery

Seo-Google Speed

Git-Bitbucket

Php-MySql

Wordpress

Sublime Text

Gulp-Npm

React-VueJS

MVC Architecture